<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>pust.co</title>
	<atom:link href="/index.php/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Pyongyang University of Science &#38; Technology</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 16:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.12</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/cropped-p-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>pust.co</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>First HSK Test Site in the DPRK opens at PUST</title>
		<link>/index.php/2019/05/13/first-hsk-test-site-in-the-dprk-opens-at-pust/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 22:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5461</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[On Saturday 11th May, 45 undergraduate PUST students took the Chinese language test HSK (hanyu shuiping kaoshi) at the newly-established test site at the PUST. Earlier in the week on 7th May, the university was honoured to receive  the Ambassador of the People’s Republic of China to the DPR Korea; the Deputy Director-General of the National Chinese Language ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2019/05/13/first-hsk-test-site-in-the-dprk-opens-at-pust/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday 11<sup>th</sup> May, 45 undergraduate PUST students took the Chinese language test HSK (hanyu shuiping kaoshi) at the newly-established test site at the PUST.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-5462 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/competitors-performers-guests-1024x494.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="494" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/competitors-performers-guests-1024x494.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/05/competitors-performers-guests-300x145.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/05/competitors-performers-guests-768x370.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p><span style="color: #00000a;"><img class="size-medium wp-image-5464 alignleft" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/unveiling-300x167.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="167" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/unveiling-300x167.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/05/unveiling-768x428.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/05/unveiling-1024x570.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />Earlier in the week on 7<sup>th</sup> </span><span style="color: #00000a;">May, the university was honoured to receive</span>  <span style="color: #00000a;">the Ambassador of the People’s Republic of China to the DPR Korea; the Deputy Director-General of the National Chinese Language Office, PRC Ministry of Education; and a delegation of other senior officials from China and the PRC Embassy to the DPR Korea. They joined the Vice Chairma</span><span style="color: #00000a;">n of the Education Commission of the DPR Korea, the Foreign Education Bureau of the Education Commission, and the senior leadership of PUST, to officially open the HSK Test Center.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #00000a;"><img class="size-medium wp-image-5463 alignleft" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/P1030381crop-300x203.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="203" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/P1030381crop-300x203.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/05/P1030381crop-768x520.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/05/P1030381crop-1024x693.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />A</span><span style="color: #00000a;">fte</span><span style="color: #00000a;">r the opening ceremony, the guests enjoye</span><span style="color: #00000a;">d the final round of PUST’s Chinese Speech Contest, followed by some recitals and ‘cross-talk’ entertainment from students. The guests then presented the </span><span style="color: #00000a;">prizes to the contest winners and congratulated the students on their excellent speaking skills, even though they have only been learning Chinese for one or two years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another semester begins for both new and returning faculty and students</title>
		<link>/index.php/2019/03/14/another-semester-begins-for-both-new-and-returning-faculty-and-students/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5300</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Yet another semester has just started at PUST. On 4th March at the opening ceremony, the DPRK-side university president extended a warm welcome to all the teachers and students, and expressed his hopes for a successful new semester. This semester there are currently around 50 foreign professors, staff and families on campus, with more due ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2019/03/14/another-semester-begins-for-both-new-and-returning-faculty-and-students/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yet another semester has just started at PUST. On 4<sup>th</sup> March at the opening ceremony, the DPRK-side university president extended a warm welcome to all the teachers and students, and expressed his hopes for a successful new semester.</p>
<p>This semester there are currently around 50 foreign professors, staff and families on campus, with more due to arrive in the coming days. We are especially pleased to welcome some new members to our faculty, including some from the UK, China and Norway, along with many returning faculty from previous semesters.   In addition, a group of 11 new graduate students have joined us to study a Masters in Medicine (7 students) and Dentistry (4 students).</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-5301 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/P1230447.jpg" alt="" width="2800" height="568" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/P1230447.jpg 2800w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/03/P1230447-300x61.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/03/P1230447-768x156.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/03/P1230447-1024x208.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 2800px) 100vw, 2800px" /></p>
<p>On March 28<sup>th</sup> there will be a graduation ceremony for 99 undergraduate students and 34 Masters students. We will be welcoming a number of international visitors to campus for the occasion.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Exciting and Successful Start to the Fall 2018 Semester at PUST</title>
		<link>/index.php/2018/10/09/an-exciting-and-successful-start-to-the-fall-2018-semester-at-pust/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 08:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=4792</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Fall Semester 2018 has got off to a good start at PUST, with 114 new freshmen students joining us. This includes 18 female students. As usual, these students begin their time at PUST with two semesters of intensive English classes, to prepare them ready for taking major subjects taught in English by foreign professors. ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2018/10/09/an-exciting-and-successful-start-to-the-fall-2018-semester-at-pust/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Fall Semester 2018 has got off to a good start at PUST, with 114 new freshmen students joining us. This includes 18 female students. As usual, these students begin their time at PUST with two semesters of intensive English classes, to prepare them ready for taking major subjects taught in English by foreign professors.<img class="wp-image-4797 alignright" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/IMG_0355-copy-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="363" height="273" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/IMG_0355-copy-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/10/IMG_0355-copy-768x576.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/10/IMG_0355-copy-1024x768.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 363px) 100vw, 363px" /></p>
<p>We currently have a foreign community of 46 on campus, comprising 28 foreign professors, administrators and families, coming from various countries including China, Singapore, Germany, Switzerland, the Netherlands, the UK and Canada. Further foreign professors will be arriving in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>One exciting event at the start of the new semester was the departure of three graduate students to travel to the UK for a five-month study programme.   This brings the number of PUST students currently studying abroad to 11, with others in Sweden, Brazil and China.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-4793" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/IMG_0366-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="353" height="265" /> <img class="alignnone wp-image-4796" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/IMG_0429-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="354" height="266" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PUST Research Lecture Series continues during the Fall 2017 Semester</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/11/14/pust-research-lecture-series-continues-during-the-fall-2017-semester/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3549</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Pyongyang University of Science and Technology recently continued the PUST Research Lecture Series that was started last semester (Spring 2017). This research lecture series is an opportunity for the PUST foreign faculty to present their research. Last week, the PUST faculty was treated to a splendid talk by Professor Federico Tenga of Italy. He explained in ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/11/14/pust-research-lecture-series-continues-during-the-fall-2017-semester/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pyongyang University of Science and Technology recently continued the PUST Research Lecture Series that was started last semester (Spring 2017). This research lecture series is an opportunity for the PUST foreign faculty to present their research.</p>
<p>Last week, the PUST faculty was treated to a splendid talk by Professor Federico Tenga of Italy. He explained in detail the fundamentals of Blockchain Technology and then spoke of its most notable application -Bitcoin. Many excellent technical questions were asked about the inner working of Bitcoin, its risks, and the measures taken to ensure security.</p>
<p>Not only was this talk informative, but it was also motivational in that several research ideas were conceived for possible future thesis topics at PUST.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fall 2017 Semester Classes Start as Planned</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/09/05/fall-2017-semester-classes-start-as-planned/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 04:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3042</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In spite of various difficulties due to travel restrictions on US passport-holders and the increased tensions around the Korean peninsula, the Pyongyang University of Science and Technology (PUST) has commenced the Fall semester 2017 on the planned day, today, Monday 4th September. The initial arrangements for classes have been adapted to suit the available resources ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/09/05/fall-2017-semester-classes-start-as-planned/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In spite of various difficulties due to travel restrictions on US passport-holders and the increased tensions around the Korean peninsula, the Pyongyang University of Science and Technology (PUST) has commenced the Fall semester 2017 on the planned day, today, Monday 4th September.</p>
<p>The initial arrangements for classes have been adapted to suit the available resources and the university is continuing its unique work as the only foreign-supported university in the DPRKorea.</p>
<p>The US government has forbidden the use of US passports to travel to the DPRK, as of 1 st September, unless an exemption is granted. PUST usually has 60 to 80 foreign faculty at any one time during each semester and about half of them are US citizens.</p>
<p>With cooperation from North Korean staff we have met the minimum requirements to start the semester. PUST leadership anticipates additional faculties to join as the semester progresses. The university is actively seeking additional personnel who are willing to go to Pyongyang for short visits, to increase the number of foreigner-taught specialist courses. The US government has just published information on how to apply for an exemption from the travel ban; and the leadership of PUST is evaluating how to proceed with this, similarly to the efforts of several other organisations that have long-term humanitarian work in the DPRK and are also badly affected by the travel ban.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PUST&#8217;s Spring 2017 Research Lecture Series began with tissue engineering and ended with modern mathematics</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/05/24/pusts-spring-2017-research-lecture-series-began-with-tissue-engineering-and-wrapped-up-this-week-with-modern-mathematics/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 13:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2751</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[During the Spring 2017 term, Pyongyang University of Science and Technology has hosted a research lecture series for the PUST foreign faculty to present their research. All members of the PUST community, including DPRK faculty and students, have been invited to attend the series. The lecture series began on Wednesday, 29 March, with Dr. Eneko Axpe&#8217;s talk about tissue ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/05/24/pusts-spring-2017-research-lecture-series-began-with-tissue-engineering-and-wrapped-up-this-week-with-modern-mathematics/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the Spring 2017 term, Pyongyang University of Science and Technology has hosted a research lecture series for the PUST foreign faculty to present their research. All members of the PUST community, including DPRK faculty and students, have been invited to attend the series.</p>
<p>The lecture series began on Wednesday, 29 March, with Dr. Eneko Axpe&#8217;s talk about tissue engineering, a field that seeks to repair –or replace– damaged organs by creating functional artificial tissues.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2752 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170329_155407-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170329_155407-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170329_155407-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170329_155407-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>In his seminar, Dr. Axpe, who currently conducts research at Cambridge University, highlighted recent advances in nanotechnology and three-dimensional printing, techniques that help develop engineered biomaterials for the regenerative medicine of the future.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2753 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170329_163452-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170329_163452-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170329_163452-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170329_163452-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>The final presentation of PUST’s Research Lectures Series was held this week on 24 May with a presentation by Dr. George Sturm, the graduate Dean of PUST.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2771 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170524_161739-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170524_161739-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170524_161739-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/IMG_20170524_161739-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>Dr. Sturm spoke about the exciting investigations of the Modern Mathematics in regards to the relationship between gene expressions and breast-cancer outcome measurements. A variety of interesting analyses and their practical results were given. The seminar was particularly well-attended by the ALS graduate students since the field of precision medicine is cutting-edge. Hopefully, this seminar will be the beginning of more research into this important area.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The PUST Research Lecture Series continues in May with presentations about medical strokes and learning communities</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/05/21/the-pust-research-lecture-series-continues-in-may-with-presentations-about-medical-strokes-and-learning-communities/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2743</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Research Seminar continued in May with three more members of the foreign faculty presenting their research addressing medical research and the importance of a society to establish a learning community. On 10 May, Dr. Charles D. Sands, Professor and Founding Dean, PUST College of Pharmacy, presented an excellent talk entitled: Pulse Pressure and Mean Arterial ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/05/21/the-pust-research-lecture-series-continues-in-may-with-presentations-about-medical-strokes-and-learning-communities/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Research Seminar continued in May with three more members of the foreign faculty presenting their research addressing medical research and the importance of a society to establish a learning community.</p>
<p>On 10 May, Dr. Charles D. Sands, Professor and Founding Dean, PUST College of Pharmacy, presented an excellent talk entitled: <em>Pulse Pressure and Mean Arterial Pressure as Predictors of Stroke.</em> Using sophisticated statistical analyses, Dr. Sands investigated a life-threatening problem with the hope of finding new explanatory factors. Although the results were promising, the study re-emphasized the fact that high systolic blood pressure is the key factor in predicting stroke incidence. For younger researchers, the presentation gave an excellent overview on how a research project should be properly structured, how good data collection is essential, and how proper statistical analyses are absolutely necessary.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2744 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170510_163127-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170510_163127-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170510_163127-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170510_163127-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>On 17 May, Casey Robinson, PhD Candidate at Waseda University, spoke about the importance of establishing a learning society for the financial benefits of a society. Professor Robinson addressed many aspects of this problem including economic and social factors. Since he is in the beginning stages of his dissertation research, he welcomed the professional feedback from the seminar attendees on how to better focus and improve his research aims.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2745 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170517_155725-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170517_155725-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170517_155725-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170517_155725-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The PUST Research Lecture Series continues with presentations about business, computer science, and science diplomacy</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/05/19/the-pust-research-lecture-series-continues-with-presentations-about-business-computer-science-and-science-diplomacy/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 21:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2738</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Research Seminar Series continued through the month of April with several members of the foreign faculty presenting their research to the PUST faculty and community. On 19 April, Dr. John Robinson, who recently received his Ph.D. degree, spoke about his dissertation results. He gave an interesting overview of how Asian social networking impacts the ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/05/19/the-pust-research-lecture-series-continues-with-presentations-about-business-computer-science-and-science-diplomacy/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Research Seminar Series continued through the month of April with several members of the foreign faculty presenting their research to the PUST faculty and community.</p>
<p>On 19 April, Dr. John Robinson, who recently received his Ph.D. degree, spoke about his dissertation results. He gave an interesting overview of how Asian social networking impacts the business world. It was a very thought-provoking talk, especially for the non-Asian listeners, and gave everyone a new perspective on how to be more effective in their interactions with potential business and professional partners.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2739 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170419_162220-1-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170419_162220-1-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170419_162220-1-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170419_162220-1-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>On 26 April, Dr. Wesley Brewer, Vice President of Research, gave an excellent talk on genetic entropy. He discussed his research and efforts to develop state-of-the-art numerical simulation software to study genetic entropy that is the accumulation of mutations in the genome.  Dr. Brewer illustrated the practical use of his theoretical results and how they relate to longevity and diseases. He also spoke about applications in precision medicine that attempt to predict cancer based on gene expression levels. It was a very informative and challenging talk.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2740 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170426_163105-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170426_163105-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170426_163105-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170426_163105-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>On Wednesday, 3 May 2017, the PUST Lecture Series was honored to host our esteemed Chancellor, Dr. Chan-Mo Park. Chancellor Park shared many highlights of his long career with the attendees of the seminar. Besides emphasizing the importance of computer technology, Dr. Park discussed the activities of his later years regarding science diplomacy. His concluding remarks concerning the need for patience and the heart of a servant left a big impression on the faculty.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2741 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170503_155545-1024x768.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170503_155545-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170503_155545-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/05/20170503_155545-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The PUST Research Lecture Series continues with a presentation about herbicides and weed control methods</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/04/12/the-pust-research-lecture-series-continues-with-a-presentation-about-herbicides-and-weed-control-methods/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2517</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Pyongyang University of Science and Technology continues our research lecture series with a presentation from Dr. Glenn Wehtje, research agronomist at Auburn University (USA). Glenn spoke about his research in herbicides and weed control methods. He specifically outlined three different projects and how he carefully designed the experiments to maximize his data collection efforts, how he ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/04/12/the-pust-research-lecture-series-continues-with-a-presentation-about-herbicides-and-weed-control-methods/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pyongyang University of Science and Technology continues our research lecture series with a presentation from Dr. Glenn Wehtje, research agronomist at Auburn University (USA).</p>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-2518 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/20170412_164917-e1491997711692-225x300.jpg" alt="" width="225" height="300" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/20170412_164917-e1491997711692-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/04/20170412_164917-e1491997711692-768x1024.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" /></p>
<p>Glenn spoke about his research in herbicides and weed control methods. He specifically outlined three different projects and how he carefully designed the experiments to maximize his data collection efforts, how he measured the response variables, how he analyzed the data using sophisticated statistical methods, and how he interpreted the results. He also discussed the practical implications of each of these three projects. Overall, it was a well-rounded presentation based upon theory, yet loaded with practical applications.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introducing the PUST Research Lecture Series</title>
		<link>/index.php/2017/04/11/introducing-the-pust-research-lecture-series/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EF]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2506</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[During the Spring 2017 term, Pyongyang University of Science and Technology has hosted a research lecture series for the PUST foreign faculty to present their research. All members of the PUST community, including DPRK faculty and students, are invited to attend the series. In the second lecture seminar, Adjunct Assistant Professor Dominik Naeher of Germany presented his ... <a class="read-more" href="/index.php/2017/04/11/introducing-the-pust-research-lecture-series/">Read more...</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the Spring 2017 term, Pyongyang University of Science and Technology has hosted a research lecture series for the PUST foreign faculty to present their research. All members of the PUST community, including DPRK faculty and students, are invited to attend the series.</p>
<p>In the second lecture seminar, Adjunct Assistant Professor Dominik Naeher of Germany presented his research titled, &#8220;Technology Adoption under Rational Inattention: Theory and Application to Modern Input Use in African Agriculture.&#8221;</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2507 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/04-05-PUST-Research-Seminar-1024x683.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="683" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/04-05-PUST-Research-Seminar-1024x683.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/04/04-05-PUST-Research-Seminar-300x200.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2017/04/04-05-PUST-Research-Seminar-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>For many developing countries, the diffusion and proper adoption of modern agricultural input technologies such as fertilizer and improved seed varieties remains a key factor for achieving food security, reducing extreme poverty, and triggering sustainable economic growth. The presented research analyzes the empirical role of different economic factors in this context and develops a novel framework to study technology adoption under rational inattention, an approach that takes into account psychological evidence on the limits of human cognition in economic decision-making. The goal of this work is to investigate alternative ways to support farmers in choosing optimal cultivation practices and applying modern inputs more efficiently.</p>
<p>Dr. Naeher is currently teaching Econometrics to undergraduate students studying in the College of Business.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
